<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Cllasify</string>


    <!--Account setting activity-->

    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="profile_setting">Profile Setting</string>
    <string name="option_notification">Notification</string>
    <string name="noti_config">Configure Notification</string>
    <string name="general">General</string>
    <string name="theme">Theme</string>
    <string name="more_options">More Options</string>
    <string name="share_feedback">Share Feedback</string>
    <string name="terms_of_service">Terms of Service</string>
    <string name="option_privacy_policy">Privacy policy</string>
    <string name="rate_us">Rate us</string>
    <string name="sign_out">Sign Out</string>
    <string name="contentDescription">TODO</string>
    <string name="about_us">About us</string>


    <!--Activity about-->

    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="about_contentDescription">TODO</string>
    <string name="the_team">THE TEAM</string>
    <string name="abhi">Abhijit Biswas</string>
    <string name="team_lead">Team Lead</string>
    <string name="about_cllasify">Cllasify</string>
    <string name="sohel">Sohel Sheikh</string>
    <string name="developer_lead">Developer Lead</string>


    <!--Activity attendance history-->

    <string name="attend_contentDescription">TODO</string>
    <string name="attendance">Attendance</string>


    <!--Activity create class-->

    <string name="create_class">Create class</string>
    <string name="create_class_title">Create a class for your server</string>
    <string name="class_name">Class name</string>
    <string name="hint_crateClass"><font size="15">Type here...</font> </string>
    <string name="create_class_dec">* It will create a new class in the server</string>
    <string name="class_contentDescription">TODO</string>


    <!--Activity create server-->

    <string name="create_server">Create server</string>
    <string name="setup_server">Setup a server for your school</string>
    <string name="server_name">Server name</string>
    <string name="hint_crateServer"><font size="15">Type here...</font> </string>
    <string name="create_server_dec">* The name of you education Institutions like schools....</string>
    <string name="server_contentDescription">TODO</string>


    <!--Activity create subject-->

    <string name="create_subject">Create subject</string>
    <string name="setup_subject">Create subject for your class</string>
    <string name="skip">Skip</string>
    <string name="subject_name">subject name</string>
    <string name="hint_crateSubject"><font size="15">Type here...</font> </string>
    <string name="create_subject_dec">* It will create a subject in the class, if you skip you can create subject from the server setting page</string>
    <string name="subject_contentDescription">TODO</string>


    <!--Activity edit roll number-->

    <string name="roll_contentDescription">TODO</string>
    <string name="roll_numbers">Roll numbers</string>
    <string name="roll_save">Save</string>


    <!--Activity explore-->

    <string name="explore">Explore</string>
    <string name="server">#server</string>
    <string name="school">#School</string>
    <string name="users">#Users</string>


    <!--Activity explore item-->

    <string name="explore_contentDescription">TODO</string>
    <string name="demo_school_name">Kalyani central model</string>
    <string name="students">Students</string>
    <string name="teachers">Teachers</string>
    <string name="join_teacher">Join as a teacher</string>


    <!--Activity friend chat-->

    <string name="friend_contentDescription">TODO</string>
    <string name="demo_username">Username</string>
    <string name="hint_edittext"><font size="17">Message...</font> </string>


    <!--Activity get started-->

    <string name="started_cllasify">Cllasify</string>
    <string name="started_explore">Explore</string>
    <string name="education">Education.</string>
    <string name="signInGoogle">Sign In with Google</string>


    <!--Activity notification-->

    <string name="notification">Notification</string>


    <!--Activity notification settings-->

    <string name="setting_notification">Notification</string>
    <string name="setting_general">General</string>
    <string name="system_options">System Options</string>
    <string name="config_noti_device">Configure notifications for this device</string>
    <string name="push_noti_type">Push Notifications Types</string>
    <string name="direct_msg">Direct Messages</string>
    <string name="Server_msg">Server Messages</string>
    <string name="mentions">Mentions</string>


    <!--Activity premium-->

    <string name="premium">Premium</string>


    <!--Activity privacy-->
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy policy</string>
    <string name="privacy_contentDescription">TODO</string>
    <string name="cllasify_data_policy">Cllasify Data Policy</string>
    <string name="data_policy_1">Cllasify built the Cllasify app as a Free app. This SERVICE is provided by Cllasify at no cost and is intended for use as is.</string>
    <string name="data_policy_2">This page is used to inform visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use our Service.</string>
    <string name="data_policy_3">If you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy. The Personal Information that we collect is used for providing and improving the Service. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.</string>
    <string name="data_policy_4">The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, which are accessible at Cllasify unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy.</string>
    <string name="info_uses">Information Collection and Use</string>
    <string name="info_uses_1">For a better experience, while using our Service, we may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information, including but not limited to Email, Name, Location, Institution name. The information that we request will be retained by us and used as described in this privacy policy.</string>
    <string name="info_uses_2">The app does use third-party services that may collect information used to identify you.</string>
    <string name="info_uses_3">Link to the privacy policy of third-party service providers used by the app</string>
    <string name="info_uses_4">The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, which are accessible at Cllasify unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy.</string>
    <string name="google_play">Google Play Services</string>
    <string name="admob">AdMob</string>
    <string name="google_analytics">Google Analytics for Firebase</string>
    <string name="firebase_crashlytics">Firebase Crashlytics</string>
    <string name="log_data">Log Data</string>
    <string name="log_data_1">We want to inform you that whenever you use our Service, in a case of an error in the app we collect data and information (through third-party products) on your phone called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your device Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, device name, operating system version, the configuration of the app when utilizing our Service, the time and date of your use of the Service, and other statistics.</string>
    <string name="cookies">Cookies</string>
    <string name="cookies_1">Cookies are files with a small amount of data that are commonly used as anonymous unique identifiers. These are sent to your browser from the websites that you visit and are stored on your devices internal memory.</string>
    <string name="cookies_2">This Service does not use these “cookies” explicitly. However, the app may use third-party code and libraries that use “cookies” to collect information and improve their services. You have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies and know when a cookie is being sent to your device. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of this Service.</string>
    <string name="service_providers">Service Providers</string>
    <string name="service_providers_1">We may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:</string>
    <string name="service_providers_2">To facilitate our Service</string>
    <string name="service_providers_3">To provide the Service on our behalf</string>
    <string name="service_providers_4">To perform Service-related services</string>
    <string name="service_providers_5">To assist us in analyzing how our Service is used</string>
    <string name="service_providers_6">We want to inform users of this Service that these third parties have access to their Personal Information. The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However, they are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose.</string>
    <string name="privacy_security">Security</string>
    <string name="privacy_security_1">We value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and we cannot guarantee its absolute security.</string>
    <string name="link_sites">Links to Other Sites</string>
    <string name="link_sites_1">This Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by us. Therefore, we strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.</string>
    <string name="children_privacy">Children’s Privacy</string>
    <string name="children_privacy_1">These Services do not address anyone under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 years of age. In the case we discover that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact us so that we will be able to do the necessary actions.</string>
    <string name="changes_privacy_policy">Changes to This Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="changes_privacy_policy_1">We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.</string>
    <string name="changes_privacy_policy_2">This policy is effective as of 2022–03–01</string>
    <string name="contact_us">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="contact_us_1">If you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us at</string>
    <string name="cllasify_gmail">Cllasify@gmail.com</string>


    <!--Activity profile setting-->

    <string name="setting_contentDescription">TODO</string>
    <string name="profile_settings">Profile settings</string>
    <string name="profile_settings_name">Name</string>
    <string name="account_info">Account Information</string>
    <string name="setting_add">Add</string>
    <string name="setting_institution">Institution</string>
    <string name="bio">Bio</string>


    <!--Activity server-->

    <string name="servers_contentDescription">TODO</string>
    <string name="servers_create_server">Create server</string>
    <string name="join_server">Join server</string>
    <string name="hint_server_edittext"><font size="17">Message...</font> </string>
    <string name="favorite">Favorite</string>
    <string name="server_setting">Server setting</string>
    <string name="server_attendance">Attendance</string>
    <string name="server_notification">Notification</string>
    <string name="server_friends">Friends</string>
    <string name="server_teachers">Teachers</string>
    <string name="server_students">Students</string>
    <string name="exam">Exam</string>
    <string name="result">Result</string>


    <!--Activity server join req-->

    <string name="servers_req">Server request</string>
    <string name="req_student">Student</string>
    <string name="req_teacher">Teacher</string>
    <string name="req_contentDescription">TODO</string>


    <!--Activity server setting specifics-->

    <string name="specifics_contentDescription">TODO</string>
    <string name="server_profile_settings">Server profile settings</string>
    <string name="change_dp">Change profile photo</string>
    <string name="specifics_server_name">Server name</string>
    <string name="hint_serverName"><font size="15">Server name...</font> </string>
    <string name="server_des">Server Description</string>
    <string name="hint_serverDescription"><font size="15">Server description...</font> </string>
    <string name="hint_serverEmail"><font size="15">Server email...</font> </string>
    <string name="server_email">Server email</string>
    <string name="server_email_des">* If you don\'t set the email then no one will be able to                           take admission</string>
    <string name="delete_server">Delete server</string>
    <string name="delete_server_des">* After deleting the server, that members who are joined in it will also be deleted automatically you can never recover them</string>


    <!--Activity server settings-->

    <string name="settings_contentDescription">TODO</string>
    <string name="setting_students">Students</string>
    <string name="setting_teachers">Teachers</string>
    <string name="setting_create_class">Create class</string>


    <!--Activity classView-->

    <string name="classview_contentDescription">TODO</string>
    <string name="classview">Classview</string>
    <string name="subject_list">Subjects list</string>
    <string name="classview_create_subject">Create subject</string>
    <string name="teachers_list">Teachers list</string>
    <string name="students_list">Students list</string>


    <!--Activity terms-->

    <string name="terms_contentDescription">TODO</string>
    <string name="terms_service">Terms of Service</string>
    <string name="terms_uses">Cllasify Terms of Use</string>
    <string name="terms_uses_1">By downloading or using the app, these terms will automatically apply to you – you should make sure therefore that you read them carefully before using the app. You’re not allowed to copy or modify the app, any part of the app, or our trademarks in any way. You’re not allowed to attempt to extract the source code of the app, and you also shouldn\'t try to translate the app into other languages or make derivative versions. The app itself, and all the trademarks, copyright, database rights, and other intellectual property rights related to it, still belong to Cllasify.</string>
    <string name="terms_uses_2">Cllasify is committed to ensuring that the app is as useful and efficient as possible. For that reason, we reserve the right to make changes to the app or to charge for its services, at any time and for any reason. We will never charge you for the app or its services without making it very clear to you exactly what you’re paying for.</string>
    <string name="terms_uses_3">The Cllasify app stores and processes personal data that you have provided to us, to provide our Service. It’s your responsibility to keep your phone and access to the app secure. We therefore recommend that you do not jailbreak or root your phone, which is the process of removing software restrictions and limitations imposed by the official operating system of your device. It could make your phone vulnerable to malware/viruses/malicious programs, compromise your phone’s security features and it could mean that the Cllasify app won’t work properly or at all.</string>
    <string name="terms_uses_4">The app does use third-party services that declare their Terms and Conditions.</string>
    <string name="terms_uses_5">Link to Terms and Conditions of third-party service providers used by the app</string>
    <string name="terms_google_play">Google Play Services</string>
    <string name="terms_admob">AdMob</string>
    <string name="terms_google_analytics">Google Analytics for Firebase</string>
    <string name="terms_firebase_crashlytics">Firebase Crashlytics</string>
    <string name="terms_uses_6">You should be aware that there are certain things that Cllasify will not take responsibility for. Certain functions of the app will require the app to have an active internet connection. The connection can be Wi-Fi or provided by your mobile network provider, but Cllasify cannot take responsibility for the app not working at full functionality if you don’t have access to Wi-Fi, and you don’t have any of your data allowance left.</string>
    <string name="terms_uses_7">If you’re using the app outside of an area with Wi-Fi, you should remember that the terms of the agreement with your mobile network provider will still apply. As a result, you may be charged by your mobile provider for the cost of data for the duration of the connection while accessing the app, or other third-party charges. In using the app, you’re accepting responsibility for any such charges, including roaming data charges if you use the app outside of your home territory (i.e. region or country) without turning off data roaming. If you are not the bill payer for the device on which you’re using the app, please be aware that we assume that you have received permission from the bill payer for using the app.</string>
    <string name="terms_uses_8">Along the same lines, Cllasify cannot always take responsibility for the way you use the app i.e. You need to make sure that your device stays charged – if it runs out of battery and you can’t turn it on to avail the Service, Cllasify cannot accept responsibility.</string>
    <string name="terms_uses_9">With respect to Cllasify’s responsibility for your use of the app, when you’re using the app, it’s important to bear in mind that although we endeavor to ensure that it is updated and correct at all times, we do rely on third parties to provide information to us so that we can make it available to you. Cllasify accepts no liability for any loss, direct or indirect, you experience as a result of relying wholly on this functionality of the app.</string>
    <string name="terms_uses_10">At some point, we may wish to update the app. The app is currently available on Android – the requirements for the system(and for any additional systems we decide to extend the availability of the app to) may change, and you’ll need to download the updates if you want to keep using the app. Cllasify does not promise that it will always update the app so that it is relevant to you and/or works with the Android version that you have installed on your device. However, you promise to always accept updates to the application when offered to you, We may also wish to stop providing the app, and may terminate use of it at any time without giving notice of termination to you. Unless we tell you otherwise, upon any termination, (a) the rights and licenses granted to you in these terms will end; (b) you must stop using the app, and (if needed) delete it from your device.</string>
    <string name="change_terms">Changes to This Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="change_terms_1">We may update our Terms and Conditions from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Terms and Conditions on this page.</string>
    <string name="change_terms_2">This policy is effective as of 2022–03–01</string>
    <string name="terms_contact_us">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="terms_contact_us_1">If you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us at</string>
    <string name="terms_cllasify_gmail">Cllasify@gmail.com</string>


    <!--Attendance activity-->

    <string name="attends_contentDescription">TODO</string>
    <string name="take_attendance">Take attendance</string>


    <!--Attendance calendar-->

    <string name="attend_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="attend_okay">Okay</string>


    <!--BottomSheet bio-->

    <string name="bio_change">Change your bio</string>
    <string name="bio_save">Save</string>
    <string name="sheet_bio">Bio</string>
    <string name="bio_hint"><font size="15">Hint here!</font> </string>
    <string name="bio_warning">* You can set your bio maximum 2 lines</string>


    <!--BottomSheet doubt-->

    <string name="hint_doubt_title"><font size="18">Doubt title</font> </string>
    <string name="hint_doubt"><font size="20">Start doubt conversation</font> </string>
    <string name="discard">Discard</string>
    <string name="create">Create</string>


    <!--BottomSheet doubt-->

    <string name="send_feedback">Send feedback</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="feedback">Feedback</string>
    <string name="hint_feedback"><font size="15">What would you like us to improve?</font> </string>
    <string name="feedback_warning">* We will redirect to the gmail for sending feedback…!! Thanks for your feedback :)</string>


    <!--BottomSheet institution-->

    <string name="set_institution">Set your institution</string>
    <string name="institution_save">Save</string>
    <string name="sheet_institution">Institution</string>
    <string name="institution_hint"><font size="15">Hint here!</font> </string>
    <string name="institution_warning">* Set your institution name that you are join in</string>


    <!--BottomSheet internet-->

    <string name="no_connection">No connection</string>
    <string name="looks_like_offline">Looks like you\'re offline</string>
    <string name="connect">Connect</string>


    <!--BottomSheet location-->

    <string name="set_location">Set your location</string>
    <string name="location_save">Save</string>
    <string name="location">Location</string>
    <string name="hint_location"><font size="15">Select your city</font> </string>
    <string name="location_warning">* If you can\'t able to find your location please send your city name using share feedback option under the settings page</string>


    <!--BottomSheet name-->

    <string name="set_name">Change your name</string>
    <string name="name_save">Save</string>
    <string name="sheet_name">Name</string>
    <string name="name_hint"><font size="15">Hint here!</font> </string>
    <string name="name_warning">* Help people discover your account by using the name that you\'r known by ( either your full name or nickname )</string>


    <!--BottomSheet name-->

    <string name="set_theme">Set Theme</string>
    <string name="follow_system">Follow system</string>
    <string name="light">Light</string>
    <string name="dark">Dark</string>


    <!--BottomSheet username-->

    <string name="set_username">Change your username</string>
    <string name="username_save">Save</string>
    <string name="sheet_username">Username</string>
    <string name="username_hint"><font size="15">Hint here!</font> </string>
    <string name="username_warning">* Your username become part of your custom links that let people search your profile and reach you</string>


    <!--BottomSheet admission-->

    <string name="sheet_server">Experimental school</string>
    <string name="sheet_server_class">Experimental school - Class Xi</string>
    <string name="full_name">Full name</string>
    <string name="hint_admission_name"><font size="15">Full name...</font> </string>
    <string name="phone_number">Phone number</string>
    <string name="hint_phone_no"><font size="15">Contact number...</font> </string>
    <string name="hint_address"><font size="15">Address...</font> </string>
    <string name="address">Your Address</string>
    <string name="admission_discard">Discard</string>
    <string name="admission_crate">Crate</string>


    <!--BottomSheet profile others-->

    <string name="others_contentDescription">TODO</string>
    <string name="others_name">Name</string>
    <string name="message">Message</string>
    <string name="unfollow">Unfollow</string>
    <string name="follow">Follow</string>


    <!--Popup rename class-->

    <string name="rename_class">Rename class</string>
    <string name="hint_class_name"><font size="15">Rename Class Name...</font> </string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>


    <!--Popup rename subject-->

    <string name="rename_subject">Rename subject</string>
    <string name="hint_subject_name"><font size="15">Rename Subject Name...</font> </string>
    <string name="rename_next">Next</string>


    <!--Popup rename subject-->

    <string name="example_class">Class 1</string>
    <string name="join">Join</string>


    <!--List server class-->

    <string name="list_contentDescription">TODO</string>
    <string name="list_admission">Admission</string>
    <string name="list_join">Join</string>


    <!--List server class-->

    <string name="item_contentDescription">TODO</string>
    <string name="based_location">Based on your profile location</string>
    <string name="item_students">Students</string>
    <string name="item_teachers">Teachers</string>


    <!--Toast already join-->
    <string name="already_join">You have already joined this server !!</string>

    <!--Toast attendance complete-->
    <string name="attendance_complete">Attendance has been saved</string>

    <!--Toast attendance-->
    <string name="attendance_toast">Swipe Students to take attendance</string>

    <!--Toast back pressed-->
    <string name="back_pressed">Please click on skip or next to continue</string>

    <!--Toast cant remove-->
    <string name="remove_yourself">You can not remove yourself</string>

    <!--Toast edittext-->
    <string name="edittext">Please type something to send</string>

    <!--Toast school email-->
    <string name="add_email">The server has not added its email yet</string>

    <!--Toast server create successfully-->
    <string name="server_create_toast">Click the icon server created successfully</string>

    <!--Toast server dp-->
    <string name="server_dp">Server photo updated successfully</string>

    <!--Toast server email-->
    <string name="server_email_2">The server has not added its email yet</string>

    <!--Toast signIn successful-->
    <string name="logged_in">You have successfully logged in</string>

    <!--Toast student req-->
    <string name="student_req">Class joining request has been sent</string>

    <!--Toast subject select-->
    <string name="subject_select">Please select a subject to continue</string>

    <!--Toast swipe-->
    <string name="swipe">Swipe to open side panel</string>

    <!--Toast teacher req-->
    <string name="teacher_req">Server joining request has been sent</string>

    <!--Toast this is you-->
    <string name="this_is_you">This is you</string>

    <!--Toast user dp-->
    <string name="profile_dp">Profile photo updated successfully</string>


    <!--Doubt fragment-->
    <string name="doubt_contentDescription">TODO</string>
    <string name="asked_by">Asked by</string>
    <string name="hint_doubt_fragments"><font size="17">Message...</font> </string>


    <!--Attendance menu-->

    <string name="recent_attendance">Recent attendance</string>
    <string name="attendance_history">Attendance history</string>


    <!--Bottom nav menu-->
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="tab_explore">Explore</string>
    <string name="tab_notification">Notification</string>


    <!--Class more-->
    <string name="delete_class">Delete Class</string>
    <string name="edit_class">Edit Class</string>
    <string name="edit_roll">Edit RollNumbers</string>


    <!--Disc search-->
    <string name="search">Search</string>


    <!--Group member details-->

    <string name="suspend">Suspend Status</string>
    <string name="fees">Fees Status</string>


    <!--Profile menu-->

    <string name="block">Block</string>
    <string name="report">Report</string>
    <string name="restrict">Restrict</string>


    <!--Profile menu-->

    <string name="remove_student">Remove student</string>
    <string name="make_admin">Make admin</string>
    <string name="remove_admin">Remove admin</string>


    <!--Subject more-->

    <string name="rename_subjects">Rename Subject</string>
    <string name="delete_subject">Delete Subject</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>


    <!---All java files related strings-->           <!--File name wise -->


</resources>